Guide to the Newport Restoration Foundation Records, 1968-1999 (bulk 1968-1982) RL.01440
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Financial Records, 1968-1983
  - Summary Cash Statement, 1974 Aug (2 of 2) (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Summary Cash Statement, 1974 Sep (1 of 2) (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Summary Cash Statement, 1974 Sep (2 of 2) (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Summary Cash Statement, 1974 Oct (1 of 4) (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Summary Cash Statement, 1974 Oct (2 of 4) (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Summary Cash Statement, 1974 Oct (3 of 4) (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Summary Cash Statement, 1974 Oct 4 of 4) (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Summary Cash Statement, 1974 Nov (1 of 2) (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Summary Cash Statement, 1974 Nov (2 of 2) (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Summary Cash Statement, 1974 Dec (1 of 2) (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Summary Cash Statement, 1974 Dec (2 of 2) (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Financial Statement, 1974 Dec (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - J.T. O'Connell Cash and Carry Charges, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Summary Cash Statement, 1975 Jan (1 of 2) (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Summary Cash Statement, 1975 Jan (2 of 2) (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Summary Cash Statement, 1975 Feb (1 of 2) (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Summary Cash Statement, 1975 Feb (2 of 2) (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Summary Cash Statement, 1975 Mar (1 of 2) (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Summary Cash Statement, 1975 Mar (2 of 2) (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Summary Cash Statement, 1975 Apr (1 of 2) (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Summary Cash Statement, 1975 Apr (2 of 2) (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Summary Cash Statement, 1975 May (1 of 4) (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Summary Cash Statement, 1975 May (2 of 4) (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Summary Cash Statement, 1975 May (3 of 4) (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Summary Cash Statement, 1975 May (4 of 4) (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Financial Statements, 1975 Jun (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Summary Cash Statement, 1975 Jun (1 of 2) (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Summary Cash Statement, 1975 Jun (2 of 2) (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Summary Cash Statement, 1975 Jul (1 of 2) (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Summary Cash Statement, 1975 Jul (2 of 2) (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Summary Cash Statement, 1975 Aug (1 of 2) (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Summary Cash Statement, 1975 Aug (2 of 2) (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Financial Statements, 1975 Sep (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Summary Cash Statement, 1975 Sep (1 of 2) (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Summary Cash Statement, 1975 Sep (2 of 2) (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Summary Cash Statement, 1975 Oct (1 of 2) (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Summary Cash Statement, 1975 Oct (2 of 2) (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Summary Cash Statement, 1975 Nov (1 of 2) (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Summary Cash Statement, 1975 Nov (2 of 2) (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Financial Statements, 1975 Dec (1 of 2) (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Financial Statements, 1975 Dec (2 of 2) (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Summary Cash Statement, 1975 Dec (1 of 2) (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Summary Cash Statement, 1975 Dec (2 of 2) (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - NRF Vouchers - "P" - 1976-1983 (1 of 10) (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - NRF Vouchers - "P" - 1976-1983 (2 of 10) (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - NRF Vouchers - "P" - 1976-1983 (3 of 10) (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - NRF Vouchers - "P" - 1976-1983 (4 of 10) (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - NRF Vouchers - "P" - 1976-1983 (5 of 10) (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - NRF Vouchers - "P" - 1976-1983 (6 of 10) (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - NRF Vouchers - "P" - 1976-1983 (7 of 10) (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - NRF Vouchers - "P" - 1976-1983 (8 of 10) (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - NRF Vouchers - "P" - 1976-1983 (9 of 10) (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - NRF Vouchers - "P" - 1976-1983 (10 of 10) (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Financial Statements, 1977-1978 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - IRS Audit Form 990 PF, 1978 (1 of 3) (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - IRS Audit Form 990 PF, 1978 (2 of 3) (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - IRS Audit Form 990 PF, 1978 (3 of 3) (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Water Billing, 1978 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Museum Sales Slips, 1978 Jan (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Summary Cash Statement, 1978 Jan (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Summary Cash Statements, 1978 Jan-Dec (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Museum Sales Slips, 1978 Feb (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Summary Cash Statement, 1978 Feb (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Financial Statements, 1978 Mar (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Museum Sales Slips, 1978 Mar (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Summary Cash Statement, 1978 Mar (1 of 2) (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Summary Cash Statement, 1978 Mar (2 of 2) (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Cost Accounting Statement, 1978 Mar-Dec (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Museum Sales Slips, 1978 Apr (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Museum Sales Slips, 1978 May (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Summary Cash Statement, 1978 May (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Financial Statements, 1978 Jun (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Museum Sales Slips, 1978 Jun (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Summary Cash Statement, 1978 Jun (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Museum Sales Slips, 1978 Jul (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Summary Cash Statement, 1978 Jul (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Museum Sales Slips, 1978 Aug (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Summary Cash Statement, 1978 Aug (1 of 2) (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Summary Cash Statement, 1978 Aug (2 of 2) (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Museum Sales Slips, 1978 Sep (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Summary Cash Statement, 1978 Sep (1 of 2) (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Summary Cash Statement, 1978 Sep (2 of 2) (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Museum Sales Slips, 1978 Oct (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Summary Cash Statement, 1978 Oct (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Museum Sales Slips, 1978 Nov (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Summary Cash Statement, 1978 Nov (1 of 2) (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Summary Cash Statement, 1978 Nov (2 of 2) (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Museum Sales Slips, 1978 Dec (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Summary Cash Statement, 1978 Dec (1 of 2) (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Summary Cash Statement, 1978 Dec (2 of 2) (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Financial Statements, 1978-1979 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Expense Report - Peter Kent, 1979 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Morgan Guaranty Trust Co., 1979 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Water Billings, 1979 (1 of 2) (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Water Billings, 1979 (2 of 2) (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Cost Accounting Statements, 1979 Jan (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Museum Sales Slips, 1979 Jan (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Summary Cash Statement, 1979 Jan (1 of 2) (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Summary Cash Statement, 1979 Jan (2 of 2) (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Museum Sales Slips, 1979 Feb (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Summary Cash Statement, 1979 Feb (1 of 2) (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Summary Cash Statement, 1979 Feb (2 of 2) (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Financial Statements, 1979 Mar (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Summary Cash Statement, 1979 Mar (1 of 2) (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Summary Cash Statement, 1979 Mar (2 of 2) (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Museum Sales Slips, 1979 Apr (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Summary Cash Statement, 1979 Apr (1 of 2) (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Summary Cash Statement, 1979 Apr (2 of 2) (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Museum Sales Slips, 1979 May (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Summary Cash Statement, 1979 May (1 of 2) (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Summary Cash Statement, 1979 May (2 of 2) (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Financial Statements, 1979 Jun (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Museum Sales Slips, 1979 Jun (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Summary Cash Statement, 1979 Jun (1 of 2) (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Summary Cash Statement, 1979 Jun (2 of 2) (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Museum Sales Slips, 1979 Jul (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Summary Cash Statement, 1979 Jul (1 of 2) (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Summary Cash Statement, 1979 Jul (2 of 2) (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - Museum Sales Slips, 1979 Aug (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Summary Cash Statement, 1979 Aug (1 of 2) (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Summary Cash Statement, 1979 Aug (2 of 2) (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Expenses incurred by Augusts Pimentel, 1979 Sep (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Financial Statements, 1979 Sep (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Museum Sales Slips, 1979 Sep (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Summary Cash Statement, 1979 Sep (1 of 2) (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Summary Cash Statement, 1979 Sep (2 of 2) (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Museum Sales Slips, 1979 Oct (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Summary Cash Statement, 1979 Oct (1 of 2) (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Summary Cash Statement, 1979 Oct (2 of 2) (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Museum Sales Slips, 1979 Nov (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - Summary Cash Statement, 1979 Nov (1 of 2) (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - Summary Cash Statement, 1979 Nov (2 of 2) (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - Financial Statements, 1979 Dec (1 of 2) (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Financial Statements, 1979 Dec (2 of 2) (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Museum Sales Slips, 1979 Dec (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Summary Cash Statement, 1979 Dec (1 of 2) (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Summary Cash Statement, 1979 Dec (2 of 2) (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Water Bills, 1980 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Summary Cash Statement, 1980 Jan (1 of 2) (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Summary Cash Statement, 1980 Jan (2 of 2) (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Summary Cash Statement, 1980 Feb (1 of 2) (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Summary Cash Statement, 1980 Feb (2 of 2) (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Financial Statements, 1980 Mar (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Summary Cash Statement, 1980 Mar (1 of 2) (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Summary Cash Statement, 1980 Mar (2 of 2) (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Summary Cash Statement, 1980 Apr (1 of 2) (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Summary Cash Statement, 1980 Apr (2 of 2) (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Summary Cash Statement, 1980 May (1 of 2) (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Summary Cash Statement, 1980 May (2 of 2) (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Financial Statements, 1980 Jun (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Summary Cash Statement, 1980 Jun (1 of 2) (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Summary Cash Statement, 1980 Jun (2 of 2) (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Summary Cash Statement, 1980 Jul (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Summary Cash Statement, 1980 Aug (1 of 2) (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Summary Cash Statement, 1980 Aug (2 of 2) (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Financial Statements, 1980 Sep (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Summary Cash Statement, 1980 Sep (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Summary Cash Statement, 1980 Sep (1 of 2) (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Summary Cash Statement, 1980 Sep (2 of 2) (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Summary Cash Statement, 1980 Nov (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Financial Statements, 1980 Dec (1 of 2) (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Financial Statements, 1980 Dec (2 of 2) (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Morgan Guaranty Trust Co., 1980 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Summary Cash Statement, 1980 Dec (1 of 2) (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Summary Cash Statement, 1980 Dec (2 of 2) (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Cash, receipts, and disbursements, 1981, 1983 (Box 33)
- Architectural Records, 1968-1970, 1986 and undated
  Includes diazo prints, ink on tracing paper, and photostat copies. The records document renovations to several NRF homes, plot plans of parcels owned by the Newport Restoration Foundation, and zoning maps of the City of Newport, R.I.
  - Proposed Sites for Holly Trees and Etc. [Newport Restoration Foundation]. Undated. Photocopy and colored pencil. (Oversize-folder C2D7F1)
  - [Plot Plan, 181 Spring Street]. [Newport Restoration Foundation]. [Circa 1970s]. Marker on tracing paper. (Oversize-folder C2D7F1)
  - [Plot Plan, 4 & 6 Elm Street]. [Newport Restoration Foundation]. [Circa 1970s]. Marker on tracing paper. (Oversize-folder C2D7F1)
  - [3 Division St]. [Newport Restoration Foundation]. [Circa 1970s]. Marker on tracing paper. (Oversize-folder C2D7F1)
  - [47 John St]. [Newport Restoration Foundation]. [Circa 1970s]. Marker on tracing paper. (Oversize-folder C2D7F1)
  - [34 Pelham]. [Newport Restoration Foundation]. [Circa 1970s]. Marker on tracing paper. (Oversize-folder C2D7F1)
  - Plot Plan 12 Dennison St. [Newport Restoration Foundation]. 1970 Nov 13. Marker on tracing paper. (Oversize-folder C2D7F1)
  - [95 Spring St]. [Newport Restoration Foundation]. [Circa 1970s]. Marker on tracing paper. (Oversize-folder C2D7F1)
  - 18 Dennison Street (Formerly at 64 West Broadway). Newport Restoration Foundation/Richard C. Crisson. 1974 May 2. Diazo. (Oversize-folder C2D7F1)
  - Prescott Farm, Portsmouth, R.I., Layout Plan. Newport Restoration Foundation/R.R. Long. 1970 Aug 27. Diazo. (Oversize-folder C2D7F1)
  - 47 John Street, Site Plan. Newport Restoration Foundation/R.R. Long. 1970 Nov 13. Diazo. (Oversize-folder C2D7F1)
  - 11 Third Street. Newport Restoration Foundation/Richard C. Crisson. 1974 Mar 1. Diazo. (Oversize-folder C2D7F1)
  - 20 Division Street/ Plot Plan & Fence Details. Newport Restoration Foundation/Steven Laurin. 1976 Jan 27. Diazo. (Oversize-folder C2D7F1)
  - 29 Green St. Site Plan. Newport Restoration Foundation/Richard C. Crisson. 1972 Apr 12. Diazo. (Oversize-folder C2D7F1)
  - Parcel "A" Land of Doris Duke, Portsmouth & Middletown, Rhode Island to be Conveyed to Newport Restoration Foundation. Harold E. St. John. 1970 Feb 2. Positive photostat. (Oversize-folder C2D7F1)
  - [Parcel "A" Land of Doris Duke, Portsmouth & Middletown, Rhode Island to be Conveyed to Newport Restoration Foundation] (partial). [Harold E. St. John]. [1970 Feb 2]. Photocopy. (Oversize-folder C2D7F1)
  - Potter House, 35 Green St, Restored Floor Plans [First Floor Plan, Second Floor Plan], 3 of 16. Newport Restoration Foundation/Steven Laurin. 1979 Apr 5. Diazo. (Oversize-folder C2D7F1)
  - Potter House, 35 Green St, Restored Floor Plan [Third Floor Plan, Section], 4 of 16. Newport Restoration Foundation/Steven Laurin. 1979 Apr 9. Diazo. (Oversize-folder C2D7F1)
  - Potter House, 35 Green St, Restored Exterior Elevations [North Elevation, West Elevation], 5 of 16. Newport Restoration Foundation/Steven Laurin. 1979 May 29. Diazo. (Oversize-folder C2D7F1)
  - Potter House, 35 Green St, Restored Exterior Elevations [South Elevation, East Elevation], 6 of 16. Newport Restoration Foundation/Steven Laurin. 1979 Jun 1. Diazo. (Oversize-folder C2D7F1)
  - Potter House, 35 Green St., Restored Interior Elevations [Parlor - Elevations], 7 of 16. Newport Restoration Foundation/Steven Laurin. 1979 May 1. Diazo. (Oversize-folder C2D7F1)
  - Potter House, 35 Green St., Restored Interior Elevation [Parlor - Elevations], 8 of 16. Newport Restoration Foundation/Steven Laurin. 1979 Apr 24. Diazo. (Oversize-folder C2D7F1)
  - Potter House, 35 Green St., Parlor - Restored Stairway Details [Elevations], 9 of 16. Newport Restoration Foundation/Steven Laurin. 1979 Mar 27. Diazo. (Oversize-folder C2D7F1)
  - Potter House, 35 Green St., Restored Front Entrance Details [Front Elevation, Transverse Section, Plinth Molding], 10 of 16. Newport Restoration Foundation/Steven Laurin. 1979 Apr 10. Diazo. (Oversize-folder C2D7F1)
  - Samuel Whitehorne House - 416 Thames St. - Front Elevation, Side Elevation, Platform, & Stair Plan. Newport Restoration Foundation/R.C. Crisson. 1974 Jan 15. Diazo. (Oversize-folder C2D7F1)
  - Samuel Whitehorne House - 416 Thames St. - Section Detail A-A, Section Detail C-C, Section Detail D-D, Section Detail B-B. Newport Restoration Foundation/R.C. Crisson. 1974 Jan 17. Diazo. (Oversize-folder C2D7F1)
  - Samuel Whitehorne House - 416 Thames St. - Elevation of Railing. Newport Restoration Foundation/R.C. Crisson. 1974 Jan 18. Diazo. (Oversize-folder C2D7F1)
  - 413 Thames St. Restored Plan - First Floor Plan. Newport Restoration Foundation/Steven Laurin. 1973 Jan 12. Diazo. (Oversize-folder C2D7F1)
  - 414 Thames St. Restored Plan - Second Floor Plan. Newport Restoration Foundation/Steven Laurin. 1973 Dec 26. Diazo. (Oversize-folder C2D7F1)
  - 415 Thames St. Restored Plan - Third Floor Plan. Newport Restoration Foundation/Steven Laurin. 1973 Nov 7. Diazo. (Oversize-folder C2D7F1)
  - 416 Thames St. Restored Plan - North Elevation. Newport Restoration Foundation/Steven Laurin. 1973 Oct 30. Diazo. (Oversize-folder C2D7F1)
  - 417 Thames St. Restored Plan - West Elevation. Newport Restoration Foundation/Steven Laurin. 1973 Nov 1. Diazo. (Oversize-folder C2D7F1)
  - Preliminary First Floor Plan 14 Mary Street. Newport Restoration Foundation/The Newport Collaborative Architects. 1986 Jan 17. Diazo. (Oversize-folder C3D1F8)
  - Preliminary Second Floor Plan 14 Mary Street. Newport Restoration Foundation/The Newport Collaborative Architects. 1986 Jan 17. Diazo. (Oversize-folder C3D1F8)
  - Preliminary Third Floor Plan 14 Mary Street. Newport Restoration Foundation/The Newport Collaborative Architects. 1986 Jan 17. Diazo. (Oversize-folder C3D1F8)
  - 41 John Street, North. [Newport Restoration Foundation]. [circa 1970]. Diazo. (Oversize-folder C3D1F8)
  - [41 John Street], West. [Newport Restoration Foundation]. [circa 1970]. Diazo. (Oversize-folder C3D1F8)
  - [41 John Street], South. [Newport Restoration Foundation]. [circa 1970]. Diazo. (Oversize-folder C3D1F8)
  - [41 John Street], East. [Newport Restoration Foundation]. [circa 1970]. Diazo. (Oversize-folder C3D1F8)
  - [41 John Street], First Floor Scheme 'C'. [Newport Restoration Foundation]. [circa 1970]. Diazo. (Oversize-folder C3D1F8)
  - [41 John Street], Second Floor Scheme 'B' & 'C'. [Newport Restoration Foundation]. [circa 1970]. Diazo. (Oversize-folder C3D1F8)
  - [41 John Street], Third Floor Plan. [Newport Restoration Foundation]. [circa 1970]. Diazo. (Oversize-folder C3D1F8)
  - 95 Spring Street, First Floor Plan, Plot Plan. [Newport Restoration Foundation]. [circa 1970]. Diazo. (Oversize-folder C3D1F8)
  - [95 Spring Street], Second Floor Plan. [Newport Restoration Foundation]. [circa 1970]. Diazo. (Oversize-folder C3D1F8)
  - [95 Spring Street], South Elevation, East Elevation. [Newport Restoration Foundation]. [circa 1970]. Diazo. (Oversize-folder C3D1F8)
  - [95 Spring Street], North Elevation, West Elevation. [Newport Restoration Foundation]. [circa 1970]. Diazo. (Oversize-folder C3D1F8)
  - 181 Spring Street, First Floor. [Newport Restoration Foundation]. [circa 1970]. Diazo. (Oversize-folder C3D1F8)
  - [181 Spring Street,] Second Floor. [Newport Restoration Foundation]. [circa 1970]. Diazo. (Oversize-folder C3D1F8)
  - Mill Street Plot Plan & Landscaping. [Newport Restoration Foundation]. [circa 1970]. Diazo. (Oversize-folder C3D1F8)
  - 12 Dennison, First Floor Plan (Oversize-folder C3D1F8)
  - [12 Dennison,] Second Floor Plan. [Newport Restoration Foundation]. 1970 Feb 27. Diazo. (Oversize-folder C3D1F8)
  - 49 Mill, Elevation A-A, Elevation C-C, Plan. [Newport Restoration Foundation]. [circa 1970]. Diazo. (Oversize-folder C3D1F8)
  - Site Plan, 4 Elm Street - 6 Elm Street. Newport Restoration Foundation/R.R. Long. 1970 Aug 1. Diazo. (Oversize-folder C3D1F8)
  - Plat Maps Showing Properties Owned by Newport Restoration Foundation, 43-45 Pelham Street, Newport, Rhode Island. 1968 Oct 7. Ink on paper. (Oversize-folder NRF1)
  - Organizational Diagram: Newport Restoration Foundation. 1970 Apr 24. Diazo. (Oversize-folder NRF1)
  - [Plot plan of parcels of Newport Restoration Foundation properties: O1-O5, H12-15. [Newport Restoration Foundation]. 1969 Feb 20. Tracing paper with ink. (Oversize-folder NRF1)
  - [Plot plan of parcels of Newport Restoration Foundation properties: H02, H10, O7-O9. [Newport Restoration Foundation]. 1969 Feb 20. Tracing paper with ink. (Oversize-folder NRF1)
  - [3D Map of Newport, R.I. Buildings Under Construction]. Island Realty Corp. Photostat. (Oversize-folder NRF1)
  - Property at 44-46 Pelham Street First Floor Plan C. 1969 Jun 4. Diazo. (Oversize-folder NRF1)
  - [Plot plan of parcel numbers 1A, 1B and 5]. Undated. Diazo. (Oversize-folder NRF1)
  - [Plot plan of 43-45 Pelham Street Newport, R.I.]. 1968 Dec 16. Diazo. (Oversize-folder NRF1)
  - Zoning Map - The City of Newport, R.I. [City of Newport]. 1968 Sep. Diazo. (Oversize-folder NRF1)
  - Map of Aquidneck Island & Environs. 1969 Jun 3. Diazo. (Oversize-folder NRF1)
  - [Plot Plan, 12 Dennison Street]. [Newport Restoration Foundation]. Undated. Marker on tracing paper. (Oversize-folder NRF2)
  - [Plot Plan, 47 John Street]. [Newport Restoration Foundation]. Undated. Marker on tracing paper. (Oversize-folder NRF2)
  - [Plot Plan, 34 Pelham Street (King House)]. [Newport Restoration Foundation]. Undated. Marker on tracing paper. (Oversize-folder NRF2)
  - [Plot Plan, 3 Division Street]. [Newport Restoration Foundation]. Undated. Marker on tracing paper. (Oversize-folder NRF2)
  - [Plot Plan, 95 Spring Street]. [Newport Restoration Foundation]. Undated. Marker on tracing paper. (Oversize-folder NRF2)
  - 122 Prospect Hill St., Newport Restoration Foundation (Booklet, Sheets 1-14). Steven Laurin, architect. 1978 Mar 15. Blueprint. (Oversize-folder NRF3)
  - 44 Pelham St. Tentative Plans, First Floor Plan, Second Floor Plan, Third Floor Plan. 1972. Diazo. (Oversize-folder NRF3)
  - 51 Touro Street Site Plan/Fence Detail. Steven Laurin, architect. 1976 Oct 20. Diazo. (Oversize-folder NRF3)
  - 33 Farewell Street Site Plan. Steven Laurin, architect. 1976 Dec 13. Diazo. (Oversize-folder NRF3)
  - Wrought Iron Gates, 41 Mill Street Storage. Richard Crisson. 1974 May 6. Diazo. (Oversize-folder NRF3)
  - [Whitehorn Garden Plan]. 1974 Oct 31. Pen on graph paper. (Oversize-folder NRF3)
  - Proposed West Elevation-Caleb Carr House, Reconstruction with Gambel Roof. Orin M. Bullock, architect. 1977 Nov 27. Diazo. (Oversize-folder NRF4)
  - 413 Thames St. Restored Plan, Second Floor Plan. Steven Laurin. 1973 Dec 26. Diazo. (Oversize-folder NRF4)
  - Adaptive Reuse of the Governor Caleb Carr House for Trinity Church, Elevations. [Steven Laurin]. 1977 Nov 21. Diazo. (Oversize-folder NRF4)
  - 66 William St, First Floor Plan-Alternative Design. Steven Laurin. 1977 Mar 17. Diazo. (Oversize-folder NRF5)
  - 67 William St, Second Floor Plan-Alternative Design. Steven Laurin. 1977 Mar 17. Diazo. (Oversize-folder NRF5)
  - Coggeshall House, West Elevation, South Elevation. Steven Laurin. 1977 Feb 8. Diazo. (Oversize-folder NRF5)
  - Coggeshall House, First Floor Plan. Steven Laurin. 1977 Feb 8. Diazo. (Oversize-folder NRF5)
  - Coggeshall House, Second Floor Plan. Steven Laurin. 1977 Feb 8. Diazo. (Oversize-folder NRF5)
  - Coggeshall House (Proposed Site) - 66 William St., First Floor Plan. Steven Laurin. 1977 Feb 1. Diazo. (Oversize-folder NRF5)
  - Coggeshall House (Proposed Site) - 66 William St., Second Floor Plan. Steven Laurin. 1977 Feb 1. Diazo. (Oversize-folder NRF5)
  - 66 William St-Proposed Interior Restoration, Floor Plan B. Steven Laurin. 1977 Jan 19. Diazo. (Oversize-folder NRF5)
  - 66 William St-Proposed House. Steven Laurin. 1977 Jan 16. Diazo. (Oversize-folder NRF5)
  - 66 William St-Site Plan (Proposed House Location). Steven Laurin. 1976 Dec 27. Diazo. (Oversize-folder NRF5)
  - Newport Restoration Foundation Tour Guide Map of Restored Properties by the NRF. Circa 1970s. Color map. (Oversize-folder NRF6)
  - Newport Restoration Foundation Tour Guide Map of Restored Properties by the NRF. Includes map of Downtown Newport. Circa 1970s. Color map. (Oversize-folder NRF6)
  - 51 Second Street, N.W. Chamber Elevations. Steven Laurin. 1977 Feb 2. Diazo. (Oversize-folder NRF6)
  - [51 Second Street]. Scheme A-Existing Proportions. Steven Laurin. 1976 Dec 27. Diazo. (Oversize-folder NRF6)
  - [51 Second Street]. Scheme B-Existing Proportions. Steven Laurin. 1976 Dec 27. Diazo. (Oversize-folder NRF6)
  - Westport House-Existing Conditions, First Floor. [Steven Laurin]. Circa 1977. Diazo. (Oversize-folder NRF6)
  - 109 Spring St. North Elevation-Parlor, Vertical Board Section. Steven Laurin. 1977 Mar 23. Diazo. (Oversize-folder NRF6)
  - Coggeshall House-66 William St., First Floor Plan. 1977 Mar 16. Diazo. (Oversize-folder NRF6)
  - 66 William St., Second Floor Plan, Alternative Design B. Steven Laurin. 1977 Mar 24. Diazo. (Oversize-folder NRF6)
  - 51 Touro Street, Site Plan/Fence Detail. Steven Laurin. 1976 Oct 20. Diazo. (Oversize-folder NRF6)
  - 30 Walnut Street Site Plan/Fence Detail. Steven Laurin. 1977 Jan 12. Diazo. (Oversize-folder NRF6)
  - 109 Spring Street Site Plan. Steven Laurin. 1979 Apr 13. Diazo. (Oversize-folder NRF6)
  - 109 Spring Street North Fence Proposal. Steven Laurin. 1979 Apr. Diazo. (Oversize-folder NRF6)
  - 109 Spring Street West Fence Proposal. Steven Laurin. 1979 Apr. Diazo. (Oversize-folder NRF6)